export const data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'When did you propose to me?',
        answer: '01-02-2022',
        placeholder: 'Enter the answer in DD-MM-YYYY format (example: 31-12-1991).'
    },

    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Is jackfruit a fruit or a vegetable?',
        answer: 'vegetable',
        placeholder: 'This is a very important question. Answer it properly.'
    },

    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is my favorite color?',
        answer: 'Green',
        placeholder: "This is easy. It's all around me."
    },

    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Who do I love the most?',
        answer: 'Shiny',
        placeholder: 'It can be the name of a person, place, or thing.'
    },

    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What do I like more, pizza or a burger?',
        answer: 'Pizza',
        placeholder: 'This is a tricky question.'
    },

    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Have I watched Naruto?',
        answer: 'No',
        placeholder: 'Answer with yes or no.'
    },

    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Who is the bigger asshole, Shiny or Deep?',
        answer: 'Shiny',
        placeholder: 'Another tricky question, hehe.'
    },

    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What do I eat most of the time?',
        answer: 'Rice and dal',
        placeholder: 'Answer like "Rice and chicken" (Hint: Rice should come first).'
    },

    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'How many liters of water am I drinking these days?',
        answer: '3',
        placeholder: "Answer in numbers (Hint: it's one of 1, 2, or 3)."
    },

    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Hehe, will you ever forgive me for doing this to you?',
        answer: 'Yes',
        placeholder: 'Really sorry! Answer with yes or no.'
    }
];
